Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LIX is arranged in 99 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LIX. STATISTICS
  - Sub-Series 347-0. Statistics
    - General, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 5)
    - General, 1923-1928 (Box 521, Folder 6)
    - General, 1931 (Box 521, Folder 7)
    - General. 46th Annual Report Railway Statistics, 1933-1934 (Box 521, Folder 8)
    - General, 1935 (Box 521, Folder 9)
    - General. Arguments Amending Title No. 3, Transportation Act, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 347-1. Statistics
    - Monthly Labor Review, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 11)
    - Monthly Labor Review, 1934 (Box 521, Folder 12)
    - Monthly Labor Review, 1923-1930 (Box 521, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 347-3. Statistics
    - Subscription to Railway Age, 1925-1929 (Box 521, Folder 14)
    - Subscription to Railway Age, 1933 (Box 521, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 347-4. Statistics
    - The Commercial and Financial Chronicle, 1923-1927 (Box 521, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 347-5. Statistics
    - Labor Bureau Newsletter, 1928 (Box 521, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 347-6. Statistics
    - United States Commerce Reports, 1923-1927 (Box 521, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 347-7. Statistics
    - United States Survey of Current Business, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 19)
    - United States Survey of Current Business, 1924-1925 (Box 521, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 347-8. Statistics
    - Industrial News Survey, 1923-1926 (Box 521, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 347-9. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1923-1924 (Box 521, Folder 22)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1932 (Box 521, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 347-10. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Class I Steam Railroads, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 347-11. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Freight and Passenger Train Service Unit Costs, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 347-12. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Freight and Passenger Train Service on Class I Steam Railroads, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 347-13. Statistics
    - 42nd Annual Report of Railway Statistics, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 347-14. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Southeastern Express Company Wages, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 347-15. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Southeastern Express Company Revenue Traffic, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 347-16. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on American Railway Express Company Wages, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 347-17. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on American Railway Express Company Revenue Traffic, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 347-18. Statistics
    - Fair Tariff League, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 347-19. Statistics
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc., 1923-1929 (Box 521, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 347-20. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Operating Revenues and Expenses for Railroads with Annual Revenues Above $25,000,000, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 347-21. Statistics
    - Mundy's Earnings Power of Railroads, 1923 Edition, No. 18, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 347-22. Statistics
    - Oklahoma Leader, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 347-23. Statistics
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1923-1924 (Box 521, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 347-25. Statistics
    - Consolidation, Accounting, and Revising Systems, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 347-26. Statistics
    - Information to Local Lodges on Individuals, 1924-1925 (Box 521, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 347-27. Statistics
    - Babson's, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 347-28. Statistics
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 347-29. Statistics
    - Financial Age, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 347-30. Statistics
    - Industrial Arts Index, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 347-31. Statistics
    - Railroad Consolidation, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 347-32. Statistics
    - Comparison of Earnings and Expenses, 1923-1924 (Box 521, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 347-33. Statistics
    - City Employees of Des Moines, Iowa, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 347-34. Statistics
    - Comparative Wages of Railroad Employees, 1924-1925 (Box 521, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 347-36. Statistics
    - Comparative Working Rules, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 48-49)
  - Sub-Series 347-37. Statistics
    - Earnings of Clerical and Station Service Employees in January 1924 (Box 521, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 347-38. Statistics
    - Grand Trunk Railroad, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 347-39. Statistics
    - Comparative Working Rules, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 347-40. Statistics
    - Southern Railway, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 347-41. Statistics
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 54)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1931 (Box 521, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 347-42. Statistics
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 347-43. Statistics
    - Railroads in Grand Division No. 1, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 347-44. Statistics
    - Railroads in Grand Division No. 2, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 347-45. Statistics
    - Railroads in Grand Division No. 3, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 347-46. Statistics
    - Rules of United States Railroad Labor Board Decisions Nos. 1719 and 1989, Kansas City Southern Railway, Texarkana and Fort Smith Railway, and International-Great Northern Railroad Company (Box 521, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 347-47. Statistics
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 347-48. Statistics
    - Terminal Railroad of St. Louis, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 347-49. Statistics
    - Comparative Wages on Western Railroads, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 347-50. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics Reporting Forms, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 347-51. Statistics
    - Requests for Copies of Decisions of United States Railroad Labor Board, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 347-52. Statistics
    - Signed Copies of Agreements, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 347-53. Statistics
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1924-1925 (Box 521, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 347-54. Statistics
    - Cleveland, Chicago, Cincinnati, and St. Louis Railway, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 347-55. Statistics
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1923-1924 (Box 521, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 347-56. Statistics
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1924-1925 (Box 521, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 347-57. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Tonnage Interchanged Between Great Northern Railroad and Northern Pacific Railroad, from 1896 to 1921, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 347-58. Statistics
    - New York Central Railroad Company, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 347-60. Statistics
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 347-61. Statistics
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 347-62. Statistics
    - Railroad Data, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 347-63. Statistics
    - Railroad Data, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 347-64. Statistics
    - Changes in Cost of Living, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 347-65. Statistics
    - New York, Ontario, and Western Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 347-66. Statistics
    - United States Railroad Labor Board Rules of Carriers on Free Transportation, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 347-67. Statistics
    - New York Central Railroad Company, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 347-68. Statistics
    - Boston Terminal Company, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 347-69. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission. Annual Report, 1924-1927 (Box 521, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 347-70. Statistics
    - United States Railroad Labor Board Wage Series Report No. 4, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 83)
      1924 February
  - Sub-Series 347-71. Statistics
    - Terminal Company Contracts for Handling U.S. Mail, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 347-72. Statistics
    - Digest of the Railway Labor Act (Box 521, Folder 85)
      not dated.
  - Sub-Series 347-73. Statistics
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad, 1923 (Box 521, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 347-74. Statistics
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 347-75. Statistics
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics on Number of Clerks Employed by Railroads, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 347-76. Statistics
    - Questionnaire to Baggage, Mail and Parcel Room Employees, 1927 (Box 521, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 347-77. Statistics
    - 1924 Wage Submission. Special Fund (Box 521, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 347-79. Statistics
    - Davis, H.B., Columbia University, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 347-80. Statistics
    - Wage Agreements. Foerster, R.F., Princeton University, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 347-81. Statistics
    - Adjustment of Rates of Pay on Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville Railroad, 1924 (Box 521, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 347-82. Statistics
    - New York State Industrial Bulletin, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 347-83. Statistics
    - Illinois Labor Bulletin, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 95)
  - Sub-Series 347-84. Statistics
    - Massachusetts, 1929 (Box 521, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 347-85. Statistics
    - Wisconsin Monthly Labor Market Survey, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 97)
  - Sub-Series 347-86. Statistics
    - Federal Reserve Bulletin, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 98)
  - Sub-Series 347-87. Statistics
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1935 (Box 521, Folder 99)
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 100)
  - Sub-Series 347-88. Statistics
    - Monthly Bulletin, Philadelphia Federal Reserve District, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 101)
    - The Economist, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 102)
  - Sub-Series 347-89. Statistics
    - Classification of Storehouse Employees, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 103)
  - Sub-Series 347-90. Statistics
    - Rule 42 of Maine Central Railroad Agreement, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 104)
  - Sub-Series 347-91. Statistics
    - Regional Advisory Boards, Car Service Division, American Railway Association, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 105)
  - Sub-Series 347-92. Statistics
    - Labor Laws of the United States, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 106)
  - Sub-Series 347-93. Statistics
    - Analysis of Railroad Operations, 1925 (Box 521, Folder 107)
  - Sub-Series 347-94. Statistics
    - Income in the Various States, 1926 (Box 521, Folder 108)
  - Sub-Series 347-95. Statistics
    - Employee Representation, 1926 (Box 521, Folder 109)
  - Sub-Series 347-96. Statistics
    - Report on Trade Unions, 1926 (Box 521, Folder 110)
  - Sub-Series 347-97. Statistics
    - Pocket List of Railroad Officials, 1933 (Box 521, Folder 111)
    - Pocket List of Railroad Officials, 1926-1928 (Box 521, Folder 112)
  - Sub-Series 347-98. Statistics
    - Membership Classifications. Express Companies, 1928-1929 (Box 521, Folder 113)
  - Sub-Series 347-99. Statistics
    - The Progressive, 1933 (Box 521, Folder 114)
    - The Progressive, 1928-1929 (Box 521, Folder 115)
  - Sub-Series 347-100. Statistics
    - Academy of Political Science, 1929 (Box 521, Folder 116)
  - Sub-Series 347-101. Statistics
    - The Progressive, 1934 (Box 521, Folder 117)
    - The Progressive, 1929 (Box 521, Folder 118)
  - Sub-Series 347-102. Statistics
    - Earnings of Factory Workers, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 119)
  - Sub-Series 347-103. Statistics
    - President's Organization on Unemployment Relief, 1931 (Box 521, Folder 120)
    - Unemployment, 1930 (Box 521, Folder 121)